

Mehmet Alp ER Suluova, 16.08.1992 mehmetalper120 gmail.com +49 178 3755889

Address Bahnhofstraße 11B 85774 Unterföhring Germany

MEHMET ALP ER

Working Student - Data Analyst

About Me Electrical and Electronics Engineer with more than two years of experience in aerospace, automotive and software development industries. Currently fourth semester M.Sc. student at Technical University of Munich in Biomedical Engineering and Medical Physics engaging in deep learning applications on images. Working at Allianz Technology SE in Internal Audit focusing on data analysis and reporting.

Education

2021/09 - 2024/01 (Expected), Technical University of Munich M.Sc. Biomedical Engineering and Medical Physics Munich, GERMANY

2011/09 - 2018/12, Middle East Technical University B.Sc. Electrical and Electronics Engineering Ankara, TURKEY

Experience

Jan 2023 - Ongoing, *Working Student - Internal Audit*, Allianz Technology SE

Working on data visualization and reporting using:

Power BI

Python

Taking part in:

Connecting to data source

Data cleaning

Data quality checks

Creating interactive dashboards

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021, Electrical Design Engineer, MAN Truck and Bus

Worked on new electrical systems for the new bus models using:

AUCOTEC's Engineering Base Cable (EBCL)

Siemens' LDorado Suite

Took part in:

Selection of components

System design

Electrical wiring diagram

Verification of designed systems

Feb 2018 - Jun 2019, *Project Staff*, Turkish Aerospace Industries

Worked on a project to build an aircraft in the VLA(Very-Light Aircraft) category with students from various faculties

Took part in:

Avionic instrument selection and avionic system design Electrical system design Mehmet Alp ER Suluova, 16.08.1992 mehmetalper120 gmail.com +49 178 3755889

Address

Bahnhofstraße 11B 85774 Unterföhring Germany

Software Development Skills

Programming

PythonCC#

Computer Software Tools

- Power BIGitLDorado
- JiraAUCOTEC EBCL

Languages

English
German
Turkish

Professional Trainings

Introduction to DAX in Power BI

Data Visualization in Power BI

Data Preparation in Power BI

Data Modeling in Power BI

DAX Functions in Power BI

Intermediate Data Modeling in Power BI

Data Transformation in Power BI